CAMERON CRABB

Phone: +61416529329 • Email: camcrabb1@gmail.com

Career Profile

Computer-savvy Customer Service Officer with upbeat nature and analytical problem-solving skills. Experienced in managing data entry, database and documentation requirements with excellent organizational skills demonstrated during six years of experience.

Overview

Experienced in customer service and communication. Can provide both written and verbal communication to solve customer problems, while providing sensitivity to cultural differences. Fast and motivated learner, currently building skills in a variety of IT related areas, with a focus on cyber security.

Education

Bachelor of Criminology/Bachelor of Cyber Security DEAKIN UNIVERSITY, Victoria March 2021- Present

March 2021 - Present

High School Diploma

January 2008 - November 2013

KOONUNG SECONDARY COLLEGE, Victoria January 2008 - November 2013

Experience

CUSTOMER SERVICE OFFICER/SPECIALIST Surrey Park Swimming, Box Hill, VIC

August 2017 - Present

- Managed accurate and current customer account data with manual forms processing and digital information updates.
- Managed Cash, EFTPOS and online payments, updated account balances and discussed subsequent payments with customers to keep accounts on track.
- Performed data entry across multiple databases to record call notes, track requests, document customer problems and the advised solutions, and track a variety of customer related metrics.
- Addressed customer complaints and mitigated dissatisfaction by employing timely and effective solutions.
- <u>In specialist role</u>, responsible for education of staff and customers on best practices when using our software.
- <u>In specialist role</u>, responsible for providing IT assistance to other staff and customers.
- <u>In specialist role</u>, responsible for creating and maintaining a variety of python programs to help with work productivity and efficiency.

INDUSTRY PLACEMENT ROLE

K7 Computing, Chennai, India

November 2022 - December 2022

- Perform demonstrations of malware analysis, network analysis, and information gathering techniques.
- Write up reports assessing files for potential malware, make recommendations on mitigation.
- Write up reports assessing network activity for malicious behavior, make recommendations on mitigation.
- Work in a team to design a data analysis tool to assess the legitimacy of network behavior.

LIFEGUARD

Genazzano FCJ College, Kew, VIC

May 2013 - November 2017

- Maintained rescue equipment in peak condition by conducting inspections and completing basic repairs.
- Learned and maintained proficiency in first responder skills such as First Aid and CPR to offer individuals in distress optimal support.
- Complied with pool policies and procedures and offered suggestions to maximize safety awareness.
- Scrutinized pool area to prevent possible injuries or fatalities, minimizing emergency situations.
- Checked water readings every three hours to keep chemicals at safe levels and avoid potential illnesses among patrons.

Skills

- Administrative and IT support.
- Programming (C#, Python, Java).
- Use of data analytics tools.
- Use of network monitoring and analysis tools.
- Use of digital forensics tools.
- · Use of network security tools.
- Use of information gathering tools.
- Use of vulnerability testing tools.
- Dynamic and Static Malware analysis.
- Effective written and verbal communication.
- Service recommendations.
- · Sales.
- Customer Accounts Management.
- Database Management.
- Account management.
- · Payment processing.

Referees

• Available upon request.